As well as working with people.
This was a good mix of both.
When you plug system science, you do not educate yourself as a profession, but to an industry,
Where you can work with different things.
Such as requirements analysts, programmers or business analysts,
or UX designer or project manager.
I was unsure and wanted a breadth with my studies.
Therefore chose to study the master's program in informatics.
I probably want to start working right away.
Initially, perhaps as a programmer and later project manager or reached.
What most people think about system science is programming and database management,
But system science is so much more.
You also read a lot of UX design and requirements management.
It is also about learning the connection between IT and man.